{
  "1": [
    {
      "question": "I'm afraid we _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being watched",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "These notes _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being write"
    },
    {
      "question": "The picture _____ by the artist now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being drawn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "am being troubled",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am being trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being chosen",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being choose"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cake _____ at the moment .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "The article _____ now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being printed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being print"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being fixed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being fix"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being helped",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being help"
    },
    {
      "question": "The mail _____ by the postman .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being delivered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being deliver"
    },
    {
      "question": "The team _____ by the referee .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being congratulated",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being congratulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "The presents _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being opened",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being open"
    },
    {
      "question": "The criminal _____ by the police .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being followed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being follow"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being washed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "The exam _____ now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "The passport _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being checked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being check"
    },
    {
      "question": "The door _____ now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being closed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being close"
    },
    {
      "question": "The watch _____ now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being repaired",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being repair"
    },
    {
      "question": "The highest tower _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being build"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nick’s order _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being delivered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being deliver"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our dinner _____ as we speak .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "A letter _____ by her .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being write"
    },
    {
      "question": "My articles _____ at the moment .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being typed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being type"
    },
    {
      "question": "A new supermarket _____ in the city center .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being build"
    },
    {
      "question": "The plants _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being watered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being water"
    },
    {
      "question": "The classrooms _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being cleaned",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "He _____ what to do by his sister .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being told",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "Harmful trash _____ into the lake .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being thrown",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "A class _____ by her .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "English _____ by Dean at this university .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being teach"
    },
    {
      "question": "A movie about me _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being make"
    },
    {
      "question": "Food _____ by a robot in this hotel .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "The final match _____ by everyone .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being watched",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "The kids _____ by Ron .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being trained",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being train"
    },
    {
      "question": "His interview _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "The final match _____ at Wankhede Stadium .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The next video _____ .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being recorded",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being record"
    },
    {
      "question": "Some people _____ on the road .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being arrested",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A picnic _____ by our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being organized",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being organize"
    },
    {
      "question": "A concert _____ by the band .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being organized",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being organize"
    }
  ],
  "2": [
    {
      "question": "I'm afraid we _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being watched",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "These notes _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being write"
    },
    {
      "question": "The picture _____ # by the artist now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being drawn",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being draw"
    },
    {
      "question": "I _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "am being troubled",
      "incorrectAnswers": "am being trouble"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being chosen",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being choose"
    },
    {
      "question": "The cake _____ # at the moment .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being baked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being bake"
    },
    {
      "question": "The article _____ # now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being printed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being print"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being fixed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being fix"
    },
    {
      "question": "You _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being helped",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being help"
    },
    {
      "question": "The mail _____ # by the postman .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being delivered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being deliver"
    },
    {
      "question": "The team _____ # by the referee .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being congratulated",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being congratulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "The presents _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being opened",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being open"
    },
    {
      "question": "The criminal _____ # by the police .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being followed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being follow"
    },
    {
      "question": "My car _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being washed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being wash"
    },
    {
      "question": "The exam _____ # now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "The passport _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being checked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being check"
    },
    {
      "question": "The door _____ # now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being closed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being close"
    },
    {
      "question": "The watch _____ # now .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being repaired",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being repair"
    },
    {
      "question": "The highest tower _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being build"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nick’s order _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being delivered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being deliver"
    },
    {
      "question": "Our dinner _____ # as we speak .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "A letter _____ # by her .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being written",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being write"
    },
    {
      "question": "My articles _____ # at the moment .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being typed",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being type"
    },
    {
      "question": "A new supermarket _____ # in the city center .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being built",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being build"
    },
    {
      "question": "The plants _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being watered",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being water"
    },
    {
      "question": "The classrooms _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being cleaned",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being clean"
    },
    {
      "question": "He _____ # what to do by his sister .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being told",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being tell"
    },
    {
      "question": "Harmful trash _____ # into the lake .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being thrown",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being throw"
    },
    {
      "question": "A class _____ # by her .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "English _____ # by Dean at this university .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taught",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being teach"
    },
    {
      "question": "A movie about me _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being made",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being make"
    },
    {
      "question": "Food _____ # by a robot in this hotel .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being cooked",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being cook"
    },
    {
      "question": "The final match _____ # by everyone .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being watched",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being watch"
    },
    {
      "question": "The kids _____ # by Ron .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being trained",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being train"
    },
    {
      "question": "His interview _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being taken",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being take"
    },
    {
      "question": "The final match _____ # at Wankhede Stadium .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being played",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being play"
    },
    {
      "question": "The next video _____ # .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being recorded",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being record"
    },
    {
      "question": "Some people _____ # on the road .",
      "correctAnswer": "are being arrested",
      "incorrectAnswers": "are being arrest"
    },
    {
      "question": "A picnic _____ # by our school .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being organized",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being organize"
    },
    {
      "question": "A concert _____ # by the band .",
      "correctAnswer": "is being organized",
      "incorrectAnswers": "is being organize"
    }
  ]
}